(Leonard:)Amy, it's your turn.
We need one more hit. Finish him off.
(Amy:)Here we go. Fifteen.
(Howard:)It's a hit, the dragon collapses to the ground.
(Sheldon:)Wait, wait.
(Howard:)And says...
"Mother? Is that you?
Your little boy is coming home."
I don't know about you guys, but I've been
through the emotional wringer tonight.
(Bernadette:)This may be the potion talking, but you are
one fine-ass Dungeon Master.
(Howard:)When we get home,
I'm gonna take you on a different adventure.
(Sheldon:)Another quest by Wolowitz?
Count me in.
- Sheldon, they're talking about sex.
- Oh, then I'm out.
(Penny:)Ooh, I have an idea.
(Penny:)Since it's not happening
anytime soon...
(Penny:)...why don't your character
and your character do it in the game?